(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-22T01:41:07.885443",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
聖なる夜
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
On this holy night...
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ！
Here we go!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap over!
ハイになって ハイになるまで
Get high until we turn to ashes,
楽しんできな
and enjoy yourself!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin' even beyond the sea,
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer to you.
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching...
ドキドキしたい Gimme Gimme Gimme 愛
I want my heart to race, gimme gimme gimme love!
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
We are here. Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' now!
2025.12.21 Sun / 出演
December 21, 2025, Sun / Cast
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert to watch, to a concert to meet.
ねぼらぼライブ参加方法
How to Join Nebolabo Live
ホロアースからの参加
Joining from Holoearth
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Schedule
ねぼらぼ応援セット
Nebolabo Support Set
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ねぼらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
Nebolabo Live Commemorative T-Shirt
ねぼらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
Nebolabo Live Photo Contest
聖なる夜
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
On this holy night...
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ！
Here we go!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap over!
ハイになって ハイになるまで
Get high until we turn to ashes,
楽しんできな
and enjoy yourself!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin' even beyond the sea,
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer to you.
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching...
ドキドキしたい Gimme Gimme Gimme 愛
I want my heart to race, gimme gimme gimme love!
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
We are here. Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' now!
2025.12.21 Sun / 出演
December 21, 2025, Sun / Cast
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert to watch, to a concert to meet.
聖なる夜
On this holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
...when four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
...the miracle begins.
さぁ
Here we go!
hyper jumpin’ 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's jump around!
ハイになって 灰になるまで
Get high until we turn to ashes...
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up!
hyper jumpin’ 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin'! All the way across the sea!
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
woh ... ドキドキしたい
Whoa... I want to feel my heart pounding!
gimme gimme gimme 愛
Gimme, gimme, gimme love!
woh ... もっと もっと
Whoa... More and more...
高く 飛びたいの
...I want to jump higher!
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。
I am here...
手が触れそうなほど。
...so close, as if we could touch.
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper Jumpin' now!
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show you watch, to a live show where we can meet.
聖なる夜
On this holy night...
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
...when four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
...the miracle begins.
さぁ
Here we go!
hyper jumpin’ 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's jump around!
ハイになって 灰になるまで
Get high until we turn to ashes...
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up!
hyper jumpin’ 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin'! All the way across the sea!
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
woh ... ドキドキしたい
Whoa... I want to feel my heart pounding!
gimme gimme gimme 愛
Gimme, gimme, gimme love!
woh ... もっと もっと
Whoa... More and more...
高く 飛びたいの
...I want to jump higher!
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ここにいる。
I am here...
手が触れそうなほど。
...so close, as if we could touch.
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper Jumpin' now!
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show you watch, to a live show where we can meet.
聖なる夜
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
On this holy night,
when four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
...a miracle begins.
さあ！
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's jump over!
ハイになって 灰になるまで タフに生きるんだ
Getting high, until we turn to ash,
let's live toughly!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' to the other side of the sea!
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want to feel my heart pound,
gimme gimme gimme love!
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
We are here. So close, we can almost touch.
ねぽらぼライブ re:VISION
[Nepolabo Live re:VISION]
2025.12.21 Sun
出演：桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
Sunday, December 21, 2025
Cast: Nene, Polka, Lamy, Botan
会場：HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show you watch,
to a live show where you can meet.
ねぽらぼライブ 参加方法
[How to Participate in Nepolabo Live]
ホロアースからの参加
[Participating from Holoearth]
開催タイムスケジュール
[Live Event Schedule]
ねぽらぼライブ応援セット
[Nepolabo Live Support Set]
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
[Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)]
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
[Nepolabo Live Commemorative T-shirt]
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
[Nepolabo Live Photo Contest]
聖なる夜
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
On this holy night,
when four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
...a miracle begins.
さあ！
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin'! Let's jump over!
ハイになって 灰になるまで タフに生きるんだ
Getting high, until we turn to ash,
let's live toughly!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' to the other side of the sea!
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want to feel my heart pound,
gimme gimme gimme love!
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
We are here. So close, we can almost touch.
ねぽらぼライブ re:VISION
[Nepolabo Live re:VISION]
2025.12.21 Sun
出演：桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
Sunday, December 21, 2025
Cast: Nene, Polka, Lamy, Botan
会場：HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show you watch,
to a live show where you can meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ
Now!
Hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin', let's leap across!
はみ出して 灰になるまで タフに刺激的だ
Bust out, until we turn to ash, tough and stimulating!
Hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin', all the way beyond the sea,
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
Woh oh oh...
gimme gimme gimme 愛
Gimme gimme gimme love!
Woh oh oh...
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher!
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
We are here. So close you could almost touch us.
Hyper jumpin' now
2025.12.21 Sun
December 21, 2025 (Sun)
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: Holoearth
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert to watch, to a concert to meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ
Now!
Hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin', let's leap across!
はみ出して 灰になるまで タフに刺激的だ
Bust out, until we turn to ash, tough and stimulating!
Hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin', all the way beyond the sea,
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
Woh oh oh...
gimme gimme gimme 愛
Gimme gimme gimme love!
Woh oh oh...
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher!
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
We are here. So close you could almost touch us.
Hyper jumpin' now
2025.12.21 Sun
December 21, 2025 (Sun)
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: Holoearth
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a concert to watch, to a concert to meet.
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ
Now...
Hyper Jumpin'!
飛び越えよう
Let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで 突っ走りきろう
Let's keep running until we get high and burn to ashes!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin' even beyond the ocean!
もっと もっと 近くにいきたいの
I want to get closer, and closer!
みるだけじゃない いっしょになれるライブ
[Not just watching, a live show we can enjoy together]
360度、どこからも。
[From 360 degrees, anywhere.]
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
[We're right here. So close you could almost touch us.]
ねぽらぼライブ Re:vision
[NePolabo Live Re:vision]
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
2025.12.21 Sun
[December 21, 2025 (Sun)]
会場 HOLOEARTH
[Venue: HOLOEARTH]
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
[From a live concert you watch, to one where you can meet.]
聖なる夜
[Holy night]
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
[When four stars become one]
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ
Now...
Hyper Jumpin'!
飛び越えよう
Let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで 突っ走りきろう
Let's keep running until we get high and burn to ashes!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin' even beyond the ocean!
もっと もっと 近くにいきたいの
I want to get closer, and closer!
みるだけじゃない いっしょになれるライブ
[Not just watching, a live show we can enjoy together]
360度、どこからも。
[From 360 degrees, anywhere.]
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
[We're right here. So close you could almost touch us.]
ねぽらぼライブ Re:vision
[NePolabo Live Re:vision]
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
2025.12.21 Sun
[December 21, 2025 (Sun)]
会場 HOLOEARTH
[Venue: HOLOEARTH]
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
[From a live concert you watch, to one where you can meet.]
聖なる夜
[Holy night]
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
[When four stars become one]
奇跡が、はじまる。
The miracle begins.
さあ
Now...
Hyper Jumpin'!
飛び越えよう
Let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで 突っ走りきろう
Let's keep running until we get high and burn to ashes!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin' even beyond the ocean!
もっと もっと 近くにいきたいの
I want to get closer, and closer!
みるだけじゃない いっしょになれるライブ
[Not just watching, a live show we can enjoy together]
360度、どこからも。
[From 360 degrees, anywhere.]
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
ここにいる。 手が触れそうなほど。
[We're right here. So close you could almost touch us.]
ねぽらぼライブ Re:vision
[NePolabo Live Re:vision]
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
2025.12.21 Sun
[December 21, 2025 (Sun)]
会場 HOLOEARTH
[Venue: HOLOEARTH]
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
[From a live concert you watch, to one where you can meet.]
聖なる夜
A holy night.
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
...the miracle begins.
さあ
Now...
Hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin'! Let's leap over!
ハイになって 灰になるまで
Getting high until we turn to ash...
達してきな
Come and reach it!
Hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin'! All the way across the sea!
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
みるだけじゃない
Not just for watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
...a live show where we can be together.
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want my heart to throb! Gimme gimme gimme love!
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたい
I want to jump higher and higher!
Hyper jumpin' now!
ここにいる。手か触れそうなほど。
We are here. Close enough to touch.
Hyper jumpin' now!
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live show to watch, to a live show to meet.
聖なる夜
A holy night.
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one...
奇跡が、はじまる。
...the miracle begins.
さあ
Now...
Hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin'! Let's leap over!
ハイになって 灰になるまで
Getting high until we turn to ash...
達してきな
Come and reach it!
Hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin'! All the way across the sea!
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer!
みるだけじゃない
Not just for watching...
いっしょになれるライブ
...a live show where we can be together.
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want my heart to throb! Gimme gimme gimme love!
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっと もっと 高く飛びたい
I want to jump higher and higher!
ピンポンパンポーン
Ding-dong-dang-dong!
みなさん、メリークリスマス！
Everyone, Merry Christmas!
本日はねぽらぼライブ re:VISIONにご来場いただきありがとうございます！
Thank you very much for coming to NePoLaBo Live re:VISION today!
ライブ開始はこの後19時からの予定となっていますので、今しばらくお待ちください。
The live show is scheduled to start at 19:00, so please wait a little longer.
本公演のチラ見せ部分は動画のYouTubeへの投稿が可能です！
You can post the sneak peek portions of this performance on YouTube as videos!
が！しかし！
But! However!
他のSNSは音声なしの30秒以内の動画の投稿をお願いします。
For other SNS, please post videos of 30 seconds or less without audio.
静止画のスクリーンショットや感想などは全編を通じて可能なので、いっぱい呟きお願いします！
Screenshots and impressions are allowed for the entire show, so please tweet lots about it!
はーい！
Okay!
禁止事項ですが、本公演のミラー配信並びに音声ありのライブ本編動画のSNSへの投稿
Prohibited actions include mirror streaming of this performance and uploading any part of the main video with audio to SNS...
音声なしでも30秒を超える動画のSNS投稿も禁止となっています。
...as well as posting videos longer than 30 seconds to SNS, even without audio.
ルールを正しく守って、ライブを楽しんでください！
Please follow the rules and enjoy the live show!
さあ、みんなー！
Alright, everyone!
遊びに来る準備はできてるかな？
Are you ready to come and play?
ねねが描いた服、着てる人いるかな？
Is anyone wearing the outfit Nene drew?
雪民さんたちがどんな姿で会いに来てくれるか楽しみ！
I'm looking forward to seeing what everyone wears to meet us!
ホロアースのライブだから好きな服装でライブ見れるのもいいよね
Since it's a Holoearth live, we can watch in whatever outfit we like!
スクショも撮っていいみたいなので
It seems taking screenshots is allowed,
色んな角度からたくさん撮ってほしいです
so we want you to take lots of photos from different angles!
そう、普通のライブだとうごいてみてまわったりはできないもんね
Right, you normally can't walk around and look at things during a live show.
うん、ねねたちの最高の写真、期待してるぞー！
Yeah, we're looking forward to your best photos of us!
というわけで、ライブ開始までもうしばらくお待ちください
And with that, please wait just a little longer until the live starts!
一緒にライブ、盛り上がっていこう！
Let's get hyped for the show together!
おー！
Yeah!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ねぽらぼライブRe:Vision始まるぞー！
Nepolabo Live Re:Vision is starting!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ちょっと早めのクリスマス！盛り上がっていくぞー！
An early Christmas celebration! Let's get hyped!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び出そう
Hyper Jumpin' Let's fly out
come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine bright
ハートきゅんって pump it up
Make hearts throb, pump it up
hyper jumpin' 夢の先まで
Hyper Jumpin' all the way to the end of our dreams
もっと もっと 刺激が欲しいの
More and more, we want excitement!
Hi! Hi! Let's jump! Hi! Hi!
Hi! Hi! Hyper Jumpin' Now
Hi! Hi! Hyper Jumpin'
子供くらいはしゃぐ方がお得でしょ
It's better to run wild like a kid, right?
ねねち！ねねち！ねねち！
Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!
低気圧から這い上がっていくテンション
Lifting our tension out of low pressure
ポルカ！ポルカ！ポルカ！
Polka! Polka! Polka!
酔いながら打ち返し まくるメンション
Replying to mentions one after another while tipsy
らみぃ！らみぃ！らみぃ！
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
カートを乗りこなして進むミッション
Mastering the cart and advancing the mission
ぼたん！ぼたん！ぼたん！
Botan! Botan! Botan!
このままスピード加速して
At this rate, accelerating our speed
辿り着く先に何があるんだろう
What lies at the end of where we reach?
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
Our unstoppable feelings are gathering a run-up
次元を超えて行こう
Let's cross dimensions and go
さぁ hyper jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Now, Hyper Jumpin'! Let's jump high
ハイになって灰になるまで
Getting high until we burn to ashes
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up
hyper jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' all the way across the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
More and more, we want to get closer
Woah...
ドキドキしたい
I want to feel my heart race
gimme, gimme, gimme 愛
Gimme gimme gimme love
Woah...
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
More and more, we want to fly higher
Hi! Hi!
360度、みんな楽しめてるかー！
Is everyone enjoying the 360 degrees?
Hyper Jumpin' Now
みんな、最後までいくぞー！
Everyone, let's go all the way to the end!
Hi! Hi! Hyper Jumpin'
斜めから攻めて解決クエスチョン
Attack from an angle to solve the question
ねねち！ねねち！ねねち！
Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれるチェーンソー
A chainsaw that slices through negativity
ポルカ！ポルカ！ポルカ！
Polka! Polka! Polka!
流れるコメントと掛け合いセッション
A session interacting with scrolling comments
らみぃ！らみぃ！らみぃ！
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つフリックショット
Refining aim to snipe with flick shots
狙い撃て！
Take aim and fire!
dis は no, no
Dis is a no, no
好きなら more, more, more
If you like it, more, more, more
邪魔するノイズは
The noise that gets in the way
打ち消せ bang, bang, bang
Wipe it out, bang, bang, bang
遊びたいだけ
I just want to play
アンチは無視して
Ignore the haters
笑い飛ばして
Laugh it off
蹴っ飛ばせ
Kick it away
Kick it! Jump around! Jump around!
このまま僕らは旅をして
We'll keep on traveling like this
辿り着く先に何があるんだろう
What lies at the end of where we reach?
信じた未来とリンクして
Linking up with the future we believed in
次元を超えて行こう
Let's cross dimensions and go
さぁ
Now...
hyper jumpin'
飛び超えよう
Let's leap over!
ハイになって 灰になるまで ダンシング shake it up
Until we get high and turn to ash, dancing, shake it up
Hyper jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin' beyond the sky
もっと もっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
Wow...
Woah...
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want to make my heart race, gimme gimme gimme love
Wow...
Woah...
もっと もっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
Hyper jumpin' now
バイバーイ
Bye-bye!
イェーイ！やったー！
Yeah! We did it!
みんな元気ー？
Is everyone doing well?
というわけで、自己紹介行きましょう！
And with that, let's introduce ourselves!
ねねから！ねねから！
Starting with Nene! Starting with Nene!
じゃあ、みんな、アイテムとかの準備いいですか？
So, is everyone ready with your items?
順番にいきますからね、みんなアイテムの準備してくださいね
We'll go in order, so everyone, please get your items ready!
ねぽらぼで行くからね！
We're going in "Ne-Po-La-Bo" order!
どれくらい待つ？この準備
How long should we wait for them to get ready?
ちょっと待ったほうがいいか
Maybe we should wait a little.
みんな、アイテムのショートカットにペンライト入れといてね！
Everyone, put your penlight in your item shortcut!
1、2、3、4で取り出しといてね
Assign them to 1, 2, 3, 4 so you can bring them out!
よっしゃ、4、3、2、1、はい、どうぞ！
Alright, 4, 3, 2, 1, and go!
はーい！じゃあみんな行くよ！ねねね、ホロライブ5期生ねぽらぼの「ね」、みんなの心の...
Okay! Here we go, everyone! I'm Nene! The "Ne" of Hololive 5th Gen NePoLaBo! Of everyone's hearts...
エナジードリンク！
...Energy Drink!
桃鈴ねねです！よろしくねー！
I'm Momosuzu Nene! Nice to meet you!
はい、切り替えて切り替えて！
Alright, switch, switch!
尾丸ポルカだよーー！
I'm Omaru Polka!
いつものあれ行くか！ポルカポルカ？おるかー！
Let's do the usual! Polka Polka? Are you there?
ねぽらぼの「ぽ」、尾丸ポルカです！よろしく！
The "Po" of NePoLaBo, Omaru Polka here! Nice to meet you!
こんらみー！
Kon-Lamy!
ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィです！ラミィちゃんしか？
I'm Yukihana Lamy of Hololive 5th Gen! Lamy-chan is...?
愛せない！
...the only one I can love!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そして！最後最後！
And next! The last one!
はい、みんな準備して、準備
Alright, everyone get ready.
何の準備？サンプサンプ？
What are we getting ready for? Stamps?
スタンプスタンプ、みんなスタンプあるでしょ
Stamps, stamps! Everyone has stamps, right?
ホロライブ5期生、獅白ぼたんです！
I'm Shishiro Botan of Hololive 5th Gen!
イェーイ！ご協力をいただきます！
Yeah! Thank you for your cooperation!
いただきますよー！
We appreciate it!
皆さんバッチリ決まったところで、新しい試み「Re:Vision Live」ということで！
Now that we're all introduced, this is our new project, "Re:Vision Live"!
詳しいことは概要欄やホロアースの公式ホームページを確認してください！
For details, please check the description box or the official Holoearth website!
はい、ということで、今日はでも、みんながアバターで参加してるし、
Yes, and since everyone is participating with their avatars today,
いろんな角度からのこの振り付け、確認してほしいなと思います物理
we want you to check out this choreography from various angles.
ねねの服着てる人はいると信じてるからな、みんな！
I believe there are people wearing my clothes out there, everyone!
いるいる！みんな、もっとよく動いて見せて！
They're here, they're here! Everyone, move around more and show us!
いいよ、いいよ！こっちがシャシホコになるんだね
Nice, nice! So this side does the "shachihoko" pose.
みんなとやれることなんかない？おまる
Is there anything we can do with everyone, Omaru?
えっ、何かな？よし、あれやろうあれ！
Oh, what could it be? Let's do that thing!
走りましょう、皆さん！
Let's run, everyone!
え、走る？ここから走るの？
Wait, run? We're going to run from here?
ポルカが先頭で、おーっと走ってみよう！
I'll lead, and let's run all the way around!
お、オッケー、じゃあみんな集合！
Oh, okay! Everyone, gather up!
みんな、ついてきてね！
Everyone, follow us!
じゃあ、せーので行くか
Alright, let's start on three.
せーの！
One, two, three, go!
先生、本気のやつがいます！
Teacher, there's someone running seriously!
本気のやつがいます！
There is someone running seriously!
はい、はい、はい、はい！早くしてください！
Go, go, go, go! Please hurry up!
追いつけないよ！
I can't catch up!
大丈夫？反対回り行きます！
Are you okay? Now let's run the other way!
先生、本気のやつがいます！
Teacher, there's someone running seriously!
本気のやつがいます！出遅れてる、こっち
There is someone running seriously! We're falling behind over here!
出遅れてる？
Falling behind?
はい、ゴール！お疲れ様でしたー！
Okay, goal! Great job, everyone!
みんなと走れて楽しかった！
It was so fun running with everyone!
一緒に走れることなかなかないからね
We rarely get to run together like this!
ちなみにですね、本番の曲の最中ですが、周りの人がジャンプするときとかも見えやすいように配慮してください
By the way, during the performance, please be considerate so that others around you can easily see when they jump.
ジャンプ、ピピー！
Jump! *Whistle sound*
周りの人に配慮して！
Be considerate of the people around you!
配慮して！
Be considerate!
はい、盛り上がってるところ申し訳ないんですが、
Now, I'm sorry to interrupt while we're having so much fun...
ここで、悲しいお知らせがあります...
...but we have some sad news to share...
ということで皆さん、すみません
So everyone, we're sorry...
YouTubeとホロアースのエントランスにあるポータルスクエアでの無料配信はここまでとなっております
...but the free broadcast on YouTube and the Holoearth Entrance Portal Square ends here.
はい
Yes.
すいません
Excuse me.
起きるよ
Get up.
引き続き、ホロアース
Next, in Holoearth...
ここポータルスクエアでは
...here in Portal Square...
ライブが配信されますので
...the live concert will be broadcast...
YouTubeで見ている方は
...so for those watching on YouTube...
動画の概要欄をチェックしてください！
...please check the video description!
はい！
Yes!
で、チケット持ってる、でまだこっちに来てない、ポータルスクエアのみんなは
And, everyone in Portal Square who has a ticket but hasn't come here yet...
よかったらこっちに来てください
...please come on over if you'd like!
来てください
Please do!
えー、じゃあ、というわけで
Okay then, with that said...
YouTubeのみんなは
Everyone on YouTube...
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
さわやかだな
How refreshing.
というわけで
With that said...
次からはソロ曲ですが
...next up are the solo songs, but...
まずは、誰からかな？
...who's going first?
誰かな？
Who is it?
誰かな？誰かな？
Who is it? Who is it?
俺！俺！俺！
Me! Me! Me!
誰かな？誰かな？
Who is it? Who is it?
ねねちゃん！
Nene-chan!
それではよろしくお願いします！
Well then, take it away!
みんなどんどん盛り上がっていこう！行くぞ！
Everyone, let's keep getting more and more hyped! Let's go!
おー！
Yeah!
無料パートは終了いたしました。 ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview portion has ended. Thank you for watching!